



69 Sea Street CT6 8QG



07393317815



<u>tajenwilliams@gmail.co</u> <u>m</u>

# Tajen Williams – Curriculum Vitae

# **Experience**

#### <u>15/10/2015–Current</u> Crew Trainer ● McDonald's – P.A. CROCKER

In this role my responsibilities were to regularly keep current staff up to date with their training progress completing S.O.C (station observation checklist). This also involved making sure new starters had a great introduction to their new job role as it was very often for some their very first job.

It was then my secondary duties to help support the shift manager to smoothly run their shift by being a role model to other around and be a leader when it came to looking after a section of the store such as the kitchen.

There was a period before doing the management program that I volunteered and picked the extra responsibility of delivery manager in which I had to check of deliveries, ensure stock rotation and follow on the delivery team training and procedures to ensure rooms where tidy and organized.

# 5/10/2020–27/09/2021 Shift Manager • McDonald's – P.A. CROCKER

This role involved being focused and target driven to provide a golden standard experience using my three areas of focus, QSC (quality, service and cleanliness). I had to be there to motivate crew and make the store safe and secure for both customers and staff.

Whilst overseeing the shift I was directly responsible to the food safety, cash security and being the active first aider. I had to ensure the food safety document where current and up to date. Handle cashing down tills and bank deposits. It was also my task to perfectly balance the labor costs of the shift whilst maintaining maximum sales and reducing food waste.

There was also a responsibility to ensure the equipment being used was in good working order or was being dealt with accordingly, some being a small fix I was trained to do myself or other bigger issues needing an engineer callout organized.



## 1/9/2019–20/01/2020 Customer Assistant • ALDI – Herne Bay

During my time working for Aldi, it was a mixed role which involved working all around the store. I was not specialized in one area but capable of working the entire store to meet pallet times and to ensure nothing was off sale. I needed to have quick service times on the tills to reduce the ques whilst maintaining a friendly experience for the customer.

Products on the shelf had to remain neat and tidy, rotated and clear of debris such as empty boxes of carboard. Alcohol had pot presented in such a way that the more expensive bottle had to have labels facing forward to entice the customer into making a purchase.

#### **Personal Statement**

I am currently a university student at Christ Church University just started September studying Computer Forensics and Security. This is a course I choose because this is specialized course in which after I finish, I will be capable of helping to protect, myself and others in the digital world. I am very tech savvy with computers having completed an A-Level after spending my teen years building desktops out of spares parts from old office computers.

I also have a strong passion for my motorcycles in which over the years
I have progress 125cc engines to the 4-cyclinder 1000cc Japanese
superbike I own today. Perfect conditions for me to be a hot summer
day with no clouds and clear roads.

In the evening probably like most people I like to spend my time chilling playing video games with a cold beverage.

#### **Education**

St. Anselm's Catholic School Canterbury – Secondary School – GCSE

Queen Elizabeth's Grammar School – 6-form – A levels

Canterbury Christ Church University – Computer Forensics and Security Degree – (Current)

### **References**

Christian Goddard – Business Manager – McDonald's Chestfield

christian@pacrocker.co.uk – 01227794979

